“创始吸血鬼”前情提要
REBEKAH: Previously on
The Originals...
我们的社区正遭受攻击
Our community is under attack.
她们是在向我们宣战
They're declaring war on us.
他这一生只真正害怕过
All his life,
there has only ever been one man
一个人，我的父亲麦可
he has truly feared.
My father, Mikael.
我们只需要一个能帮我们找到他的女巫
All we need is a witch
who can help us find him.
- 莎莉丝特
- 你怎么发现的？
-Celeste.
-How did you know?
如果你是来报仇的…
If you have come here
seeking revenge, don't--
仇我一定会报
从克劳斯开始
Oh, I'll have my revenge.
Starting with Klaus.
他会尝到前所未有的痛苦和折磨
He is gonna know pain and torment
like he's never felt before.
然后就剩下蕾贝卡
你悲惨的妹妹
Then that leaves Rebekah,
the tragic sister.
她马上就会发现自己深陷窘境
She's about to find herself
in quite the predicament.
洁妮薇知道你妹妹在哪
Genevieve knows
where your sister is.
贝丝蒂娜把克劳斯
藏在一个安全的地方
Bastianna has Klaus
tucked away someplace safe.
我想“永远”终究不会是永恒
I guess always isn't forever,
after all.
谁在那里？
Who's there?
我怎么会在这里？
How the hell did I get here?
- 洁妮薇
- 蕾卡贝
-Genevieve.
-Rebekah.
这么快就要走了吗？
我们还没好好叙叙旧呢
Tell me you're not leaving, already.
I thought we might reminisce.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：地狱归来之人
主演：约瑟夫摩根
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
主演：克莱儿荷特
主演：菲比托金
(CLANGlNG SOUNDS)
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
我的弟弟妹妹被抓走了，他们在哪？
主演：莉雅派普斯
My siblings have been taken.
Where are they?
你打断了我苏菲阿姨的献祭仪式
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
You're interrupting
my Aunt Sophie's consecration.
- 她怎么死的？
- 苏菲阿姨是战争的牺牲品
-How did this happen?
-Aunt Sophie was a casualty of war.
莫妮克，我建议你给我我想要的
Monique, I recommend you give me
what I want
除非你希望我把这里
unless, of course,
you'd like me to level this place
夷为平地
and everything in it.
没这个必要
制片：克里斯多福贺利尔
That won't be necessary.
我有个消息给你
制片：兰斯安德森
I have a message for you.
是来自莎莉丝特的
From Celeste.
若想找到你要找的
跟随她留下的线索
To find what you're looking for,
follow the path she left behind.
制片：邦妮怀斯
你到底想干嘛，冷血的贱人？
编剧：艾胥莉莱尔，巴特尼克森
What the hell are you doing,
you ruthless bitch?
导演：麦特海斯廷
可怜的蕾贝卡
你应该好好休息
Poor Rebekah.
You should rest.
你看起来有些憔悴
You're looking a little piqued.
不过这也难免
Of course, that's to be expected,
毕竟你的体内有着不少的狼人毒液
given the rather impressive amount
of werewolf venom in your system.
顺便问问，你对那个
狼人小伙子还中意吗？
How did you like that wolf-boy,
by the way?
我想他应该是你喜欢的类型
放荡低俗，千依百顺
I thought he seemed like your type.
Trashy and willing.
如果不是我太虚弱了
我一定会把你的头拧下来
If I weren't so bloody sick,
I'd rip your head off.
但你确实病了
But you are sick.
而照顾病人正是我的长处
And comforting the sick
always was a talent of mine.
我会照顾我的朋友
I take care of my friends.
我们曾是朋友，不是吗？
We were friends, weren't we?
我们当然是
Of course we were.
我们曾是朋友，不是吗？
(ECHOlNG) We were friends,
weren't we?
(1919年 纽奥良）
没事，没事
There, there.
身份不明的病人
Unidentified sick man.
这看起来可不妙
That can't be good.
你，红发女
You, Red.
来，喝点这个
Here.
Try to take a sip of this.
就跟魔法一样
Just like magic.
但话说回来，一个女巫施的
But then, again,
what would you expect
不是魔法还是什么呢？
from a practicing witch?
这只是简单的草药疗法
It's a simple, herbal remedy.
虽然不能阻止死亡
Won't stop the inevitable
但至少能减轻他的痛苦和肺部的负担
but it should ease his pain
and quiet his lungs.
应该能管用一阵子
For a while, at least.
这份工作你真拿手…
你叫什么名字来着？
You're quite good at this, Miss--
What was your name, again?
- 洁妮薇
- 真好听
-Genevieve.
-Lovely.
或许你可以给我一些指点
Perhaps you could give me
some pointers.
当然没问题，但我有点不明白
Certainly.
Though it is a bit odd.
一个吸血鬼来当护士
A vampire, serving as nurse.
拜托，亲爱的，我是个吸血鬼真祖
Please, darling,
I'm an Original vampire.
如果我的城市遭受严重的流感
If my city is under attack
from this nasty influenza,
我有责任伸出援手
it is my duty to lend a hand.
再说，要是人都死光了
那我吃什么呢？
Besides, if this entire lot dies,
who'd be left to eat?
你可真淘气
You're wicked.
我觉得我们俩会成为好朋友的
You know, I think you and l
are going to be fast friends.
今晚你跟我一起去一间
超赞的爵士乐酒吧如何？
What say, you join me at this swell,
little jazz joint
我在贝森街上发现的
I've discovered
on Basin Street tonight?
我们可以为纽奥良的健康干杯
We can toast to the health
of New Orleans.
我不确定
Oh, I don't know.
你，你也来吧
You, you should come too.
扮演了一整天的白衣天使
After playing angels of mercy
all day,
我们都应该开心一下
I'd say we all deserve some fun.
有何发现？
Anything?
他们四处散布眼线
They're putting eyes
and ears out everywhere.
日行者在跟我们的每一个线人接触
Daywalkers are working
every contact we got.
警察、码头工人、郊区的人
已经放话出去了
Cops, dock-workers,
guys in the Treme. Word is out.
任何想要讨好我的人
一旦找到他们
Anyone trying to earn favor with me
gets a lifetime of it,
- 就能得我青睐一辈子
- 很好，给我笔和纸
-if they find them.
-Good. I need a pen and paper.
嘿，我现在是听你差遣了吗？
Hey.
Am I taking orders from you, now?
还是说我们该携手解决呢？
Or are we in this together?
给我笔和纸，马赛尔，立刻
Pen and paper, Marcellus. Now.
我跟你一样迫切希望能找到她
I want her back
just as much as you do, you know.
找到他们两个
Both of them.
- 海莉
- 以利亚，你回来了
-Hayley?
-Elijah. You're back.
有什么发…现吗？
Did you find anything?
怎么回事？
What is happening?
我要你把这些名字列个清单
拜托了
I need you to make a list
of these names. Please.
好的
Okay.
“莎宾”
以利亚，这是什么？
"Sabine."
Elijah, what is this?
我觉得这些应该是
I believe they represent the names
过去两百年里
莎莉丝特寄身的女人的名字
of women Celeste inhabited
for the past two centuries.
这叫做猜谜
是种传统游戏，有点类似谜语
It's called the devinette.
It's old-school, kind of a riddle.
女巫用这个方法教孩子
Witches use them
to teach their kids.
解开谜语，文字便会消失
Solve it and it disappears.
为什么？这么做有什么意义？
Why? What's the point?
莎莉丝特强迫我
在你和我的弟妹之间做出选择
Celeste forced me to make a choice
between yourself and my siblings
现在她要嘲笑我的选择
and now, she means to mock
that choice,
用一个小孩子的游戏嘲讽我
taunting me with a childish game.
游戏时间越长，他们受越多苦
The longer the game,
the more they suffer.
要找到尼克劳斯和蕾贝卡
我们得解开这个谜
So, to find Niklaus and Rebekah,
we need to solve this riddle.
谜底就在这些名字里
The solution lies
somewhere in these names.
莎宾旁边的名字“安妮拉福勒”
The name next to Sabine,
"Annie LaFleur."
她是个女巫，在一年多以前
被族群孤立
She's a witch that was shunned
from her coven just over a year ago.
不知道什么原因，但我会查明
I never knew why
but I can find out.
可怜的东西
GENEVlEVE: You poor thing.
别担心，我是来帮你的
Don't worry.
I'm here to help.
安妮是个好女孩
MAN: Annie was a good girl.
女巫们冤枉她了，不该那样孤立她
Witches done her wrong,
shunning her like that.
她们说安妮使用黑魔法
这绝不可能
Saying that she's doing dark magic.
There's no way.
但她们有证据
They had proof.
所以她了结了自己
So she just quit.
我实在是不能因此责备她
I can't really blame her for that.
因为一旦你被孤立
Because once you've been shunned,
那还有什么理由继续活下去呢，对吧？
what's the point of going on?
You know?
- 她自杀了？
- 对
-She killed herself?
-ELlJAH: Yes.
确切地说，她投入了密西西比河
Drowned herself in the Mississippi
to be precise.
很显然，莎莉丝特厌倦了那副身躯
Celeste had clearly tired
of the body
并已准备寄身莎宾
and was ready to take Sabine's.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
她跳河自杀的地方
She leapt to her death
from the very location
就是我跟莎莉丝特初吻的地方
Celeste and I had our first kiss.
真够诗意的，用这种恐怖的
复仇性的方式
Poetic, I guess,
in a creepy, vendetta kind of way.
那些名字，那些生命
All these names,
these lives, stolen,
莎莉丝特偷走它们就为了复仇
that Celeste might take her revenge.
我们似乎别无选择
只能继续追查
I suppose we have no choice
but to see where they take us.
海莉，我先挂了，回头打给你
Hayley, I have to go.
I'll call you back.
- 以利亚，等等
- 怎么了？
-Elijah, wait.
-What is it?
问问马赛尔知不知道名单上的一个人
Ask Marcel if he knows anything
about a name on that list.
布琳德弗罗
Brynne Deveraux.
苏菲说对新月狼族下诅咒的
Sophie said that it was
her family's bloodline
是她家族里的一个成员
that put the curse
on the Crescent Wolves
但莎莉丝特说只有她能够破解
but Celeste said that she was
the only one that could break it.
如果布琳德弗罗下咒的时候
If Brynne Deveraux
was actually Celeste,
其实是莎莉丝特
那么也许莎莉丝特能够解除
when she cast the spell, then,
maybe Celeste can still break it.
我问问他吧
I'll see what he knows.
以利亚
Elijah?
我很抱歉让你经历这些事
I'm really sorry
that you're going through this.
要是我知道莎莉丝特会逼你选择救谁…
If I'd known that Celeste
had made you choose who to help--
你会葬身火海的，海莉
You were going to die in that fire,
Hayley,
我弟弟的孩子也一样
along with my brother's child.
我别无选择
There was no choice.
我的伤口没有自愈
My wound isn't healing.
那把刀里有着很强大的黑魔法
The amount of dark magic
contained in that blade,
完全恢复需要一段时间
it's gonna take a little while.
你也是其中一员吧？
You're one of them, aren't you?
死而复生的女巫
想要复仇
The witches back from the dead,
seeking vengeance.
为什么对我仁慈？
Why show me kindness?
你没有伤害过我
You never did anything to me.
而且，看到你这样
And the truth is,
seeing you like this,
我不由得同情你
I can't help but pity you.
那就背叛其他人站到我这边吧
Well, then, betray the others
and stand with me.
我会给你
你无法想像的丰厚报酬
I will reward you
in ways you cannot possibly fathom.
克劳斯米卡森居然要求跟我做交易？
Klaus Mikaelson offering a deal
to little, old me?
我真是受宠若惊啊
I should be flattered.
不过…
我们得先聊聊你妹妹的事
But first, we need to have a talk
about your sister.
蕾贝卡跟你没关系
如果你敢伤害她…
Rebekah is of no concern to you.
If you mean to harm her...
你这哥哥对她可真好
(GROANS)
The protective brother.
真遗憾，她对你可不那么忠诚
Shame that loyalty
isn't reciprocated.
不过，我也许没资格评判她
But then, I'm no stranger
to Rebekah's treachery.
我们也都曾背叛过别人
Something you and l
have in common.
来，喝了吧
Here. Drink.
我是想帮你
治好你
I'm just trying to help you.
Heal you.
让你看到真相
Get you to see the truth
其实这一百年来，真相一直在你眼前
that's been right in front of you
for almost a century.
你妹妹昨晚和一群狼
Your sister had
an unfortunate run-in
发生了惨烈的冲突
with some wolves, last night.
我想你尝到她血中的毒液了
I imagine you're tasting the venom
in her blood.
只有这样我才能让你看到
你应该看到的真相
It's the only way I can show you
what you need to see.
在她虚弱的时候
In her weakened state,
我才能帮她回忆往事
I'll be able to guide her
down Memory Lane.
这就是我复仇的方式
That's how I'm gonna have
my revenge.
让你看看她的背叛
By showing you her betrayal.
尼克劳斯
Niklaus.
马赛尔，放尊重点
Marcel.
Have some respect.
他们应该不会介意
Yeah, I don't think they mind.
你跟洁妮薇谈施咒的事了吗？
Did you ask Genevieve
about doing the spell?
我会的，现在时机未到
I will.
When the time is right.
蕾贝卡
几周来，你一直在那女巫身边转
Rebekah. You been hanging
around that witch for weeks
等待着合适时机
waiting for the time to be right.
她不应该成为你的朋友
She wasn't supposed
to become your sidekick.
只要一个咒语，我们就能真正
One little spell
and we could finally be together,
在一起了
for real.
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
她是个好女孩，就这样
She's a sweet girl, is all.
你非要弄个明白
其实利用她令我很难受
If you must know,
I feel badly for using her.
那我们就再找别的女巫
Then, we'll find another witch.
一个用不着你跟她假装友好的
One you don't have to fake
a friendship with.
除非你改变主意了
Unless you changed your mind.
我想我们有自己的家，同床共枕
I want to wake up with you
in our home,
醒来有你在身边
in the bed that we share.
我想和你一起散步
I want to walk down the street
with you by my side
让所有人都知道，你是我的
我是你的
so that everyone knows
that you are mine and I am yours.
我不想因为爱你而活在
I don't want to be afraid
担心哥哥怎么对付我的惶恐中
of what my brother will do to me
for loving you.
如果这是唯一的一办法，那么…
If this is the only way to get it, then...
我不会改变心意
No, my mind hasn't changed.
我不知道有人在这里
真对不起
I didn't know anyone was in here,
I'm so sorry.
洁妮薇
Genevieve.
洁妮薇，等等
Genevieve, wait.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这就是你说的背叛啊
So, this is your great betrayal?
我妹妹和马赛尔
My sister and Marcel,
他们背着我偷偷摸摸
they've been sneaking around
behind my back
在一起厮混了两百年
for the better part
of two centuries.
是的，全然无视你的警告
Yes.
Against all your warnings.
你曾为此教训过他们
不是吗？
You'd disciplined them for it, before,
had you not?
一定很严厉，我明白
Harshly, I understand.
- 我有我的理由
- 你不需要说服我
-I have my reasons.
-Oh, you don't have to convince me.
依我看
你只需要一个理由
As far as I'm concerned,
you only needed one.
就是对你有好处
That it suited you.
你读过“旧约”吗，尼克？
Have you ever read
the Old Testament, Nik?
你瞧
You see...
上帝不是因为有道理才强大
...God wasn't powerful
because he was right.
而是因为强大才有道理
He was right
because he was powerful.
我不知道你在玩什么花样
I don't know what you're playing at.
但如果让我和我妹反目
But if the sum total of your plan
to turn me against my sister
是你整个计划的目的
was this revelation,
那你就白费力气了
this will have been
a wholly ineffective endeavor.
可怜的家伙
You poor thing.
一千年过去了
After a thousand years,
你们家族的虚伪本性依旧
dishonesty from your family
has come to be expected.
我倒希望他们的背叛行为不过如此
I wish that was the sum total
of their treachery.
不幸的是，不止如此
Unfortunately, it's not.
你想要我怎么样？
(STAMMERlNG) What do
you want from me?
我想你对这猪圈很熟悉吧
Well, I assume you're familiar
with this pigsty.
被称为“坑”真是再合适不过
Quite appropriately known
as "The Pit."
是这样，很不巧的
几周前
See, awkwardly enough,
only weeks ago,
有一群像你这样的人类
a group of human beings,
just like yourself,
杀了许多现在站在你面前的
slaughtered many of the companions
of the vampires
吸血鬼的同伴
that you see assembled
before you here.
你在市政厅掌管档案室
You run the records room
at City Hall.
听说前任市长有一份关于
We're told the former mayor
kept a detailed record
超自然群体的详细记录
of the supernatural community.
一份列有女巫、狼人和吸血鬼的名单
A ledger of names of witches,
werewolves and vampires,
确切说，是他们的死亡名单
specifically, their death records.
我们需要它
We need it.
我不知道它在哪里
I don't know where it is.
我想大家都知道这是唬人的
你们有谁饿了吗？
I think we both know that's a fib.
Anyone feeling hungry?
好吧，好吧，等一下
(VAMPlRES SNARLlNG)
Okay, okay, wait.
市长死后，他们就把档案转移了
They moved the records
after the mayor died.
存放在圣安妮教堂的圣器室里
They're at the sacristy
of Saint Anne's Church.
瞧
You see?
乖
There.
也没多难，对吧？
Wasn't so difficult now, was it?
很不顺的一天？
Rough day?
瞧你，小贝卡
你的伤口看起来好吓人
Oh, Beks.
Those bites are looking nasty.
为什么要让我回到过去？
我们都知道结局如何
Why make me relive the past?
We both know how it ends.
你和我知道
You and I both know.
但我想你哥哥应该会想知道我们的故事
But I thought your brother
might like to hear our story.
所以我把你们俩的意识连结起来了
你自己会告诉他一切的
So I linked your mind to his.
You're gonna show him everything.
不，别这样对我，我什么都答应你
No. No, please, don't do that to me,
I'll do anything.
太迟了，朋友
It's too late, friend.
马赛尔，这里又有一个名单中的名字
布琳德弗罗
Marcel, here's another name
from our list, "Brynne Deveraux"?
这里说她20多年前自己溺水而亡
Says here she drowned herself
some 20 years ago.
你认得这名字吗？
Do you recognize the name?
布琳？是啊，我们曾经一起玩过
寻欢作乐什么的
Brynne? Yeah, yeah, we used
to hang out, knock around a bit.
细节就不用说了
You can spare me the details,
please.
她那时偶尔为我施一些咒语
She used to do some spells for me
now and then.
很厉害的一个女孩
Girl had power.
就因为一个狼群惹了我
Cursed a whole pack
of werewolves
就把他们全部诅咒了
just because
they were pissing me off.
说到这个…
Speaking of...
你认为当克劳斯发现你不顾他受折磨
What do you think Klaus is gonna do
赶去救海莉和她的狼人朋友
once he finds out
that you left him to suffer,
他会是什么反应？
while you saved Hayley
and her wolf friends.
与你无关的事我们就别讨论了吧
Let's avoid discussing matters
that are not your concern,
好吗，马赛勒斯？
shall we, Marcellus?
得了吧，以利亚
这个城市里到处都是我的人
Oh, come on, Elijah.
I got guys all over this city.
你真以为我不知道
You honestly think that I don't know
新月族的狼人们昨晚在种植园
that the Crescent Wolves
had a little family reunion
举行了家庭聚会吗？
out at the plantation last night?
顺便谢谢你让那房子烧毁了
也算是个解脱
Thanks for letting the house burn,
by the way. Good riddance.
但我要问的是
海莉为什么会和那些人在一起？
But my question is:
What's Hayley doing with that bunch?
马赛尔，我知道你之前
与这里的狼群不合
Marcel, I'm aware of your history
with this city's wolves
我也希望你明白
如果你敢打海莉的主意
and I assume you understand that
if you lay a finger upon Hayley,
那将成为你在这世上的绝响
it will be the last thing you do
on this Earth.
好，看来我触碰到禁区了
Okay. I see I hit a nerve.
我还以为我们相处得不错呢
And just when we were getting along.
我们猜对了
We were right.
我身上的每一个名字
都是死于自杀的女巫
Every name upon my flesh
signifies a witch who died
除了一个人
by her own hand, all but one.
克莱拉桑莫林
"Clara Summerlin."
- 有印象吗？
- 没有
-Ring any bells?
-None.
好吧
如果她不是死于自杀
Okay, well,
if she didn't off herself,
- 那是怎么死的呢？
- 流感，1919年的流行病
-then how'd she die?
-lnfluenza. Epidemic of 1919.
看来我们找到答案了
I suppose we have our answer.
只是不知道这答案的含义
Only I have no idea what it means.
不要，拜托
(GASPS)
Please.
你妹妹与马赛尔的私会仅仅是个开始
Your sister's tryst with Marcel
was only the beginning.
你看，你身上背负的谴责
You see,
the burden of your condemnation
太多了
had become too great.
因此，你内心最深的恐惧成为了现实
And as a result,
your deepest fear came to pass.
那就是他们对彼此的爱
远远超过了他们对你的爱
That their love for each other
would overshadow their love for you.
还转化成为恨
Turn it into hate.
尼克，他们密谋永远摆脱掉你
Nik, they conspired
to rid themselves of you for good.
你绝对不是
You're anything but.
好，下一轮我请
Okay, next round's on me.
克莱拉桑莫林，不要啦
我会醉的
Clara Summerlin, no.
I'll be soused.
能喝就喝吧，这可是城里仅剩的美酒了
Get it, while you can,
it's the last real gin in the city.
酒保
Bartender?
你和我初次见你时想像的
You're nothing like
I thought you'd be
一点都不像
when I first met you.
从小我就被教导，你们这种生物都是…
I was brought up
to think your kind were--
- 那个…
- 天生的怪物吗？
-Well...
-An abomination of nature?
你绝对不是
You're anything but.
不只是你，你全家都很…
Not just you,
your whole family is so...
优雅
...elegant.
是啊，我同意，以利亚确实无可挑剔
Yes, I agree,
Elijah is quite peerless.
我不知道，我是说，他很好，但是…
I don't know, I mean,
he's nice and all.
如果只能让我选一个米卡森家的男人…
But if I had to go
for one Mikaelson boy.
克劳斯？
Klaus?
洁妮薇，谁会想到
像你这样圣洁的小女巫
Genevieve, who would've thought
a saintly, little witch like you
会喜欢坏小子呢？
would go for the bad boys?
我就知道我们一定会成为朋友
I knew
we were destined to be friends.
麻烦给我马丁尼
Martini, please.
别动，拜托
Don't move. Please.
让我来吧
Allow me.
留着吧，送你了
Keep it.
It's yours.
米卡森家有很多人呢
Well,
there's a load of us Mikaelsons.
如果你喜欢坏小子
你一定会喜欢我哥哥柯尔
If you like bad boys,
you'd love my brother, Kol.
那你这位神秘的哥哥在哪呢？
And where is this mystery brother
of yours?
一言难尽
It's complicated.
正如其他兄弟姊妹一样
我们也起起落落的
Like all siblings,
we've had our ups and downs.
家族争斗
Family feuds.
事实上，我正在考虑
In fact,
I was thinking of reaching out
要去联络一个很久没见的人
to someone we haven't seen
in a very long while.
我希望也许你能帮我找到他
I was hoping that maybe
you could help me contact them.
但一定要保密
不能让任何人知道
But it would have to be a surprise.
No one could know.
当然
Of course.
你是要我找你哥哥柯尔吗？
You want me
to find your brother, Kol?
其实我是要你找麦可
我们的父亲
Actually, I'd like you to find Mikael.
Our father.
- 够了，不要再骗人了
- 不要怪送信人
Enough of your lies!
GENEVlEVE: Don't dismember
the messenger.
你内心一定知道
至少怀疑过
Part of you must have known.
Suspected, at least.
你父亲曾在1919年
来到纽奥良要杀你
Your father came
to New Orleans in 1919 to kill you.
是不是？
Did he not?
当城市烧毁时，他差点就成功了
And as the city burned,
he nearly succeeded.
多年来
My family and l
我和我的家人对彼此做了许多可怕的事
have done some terrible things
to each other over the years.
但蕾贝卡绝对不会找我的父亲
But Rebekah
would not call my father.
不管她有多么愤怒
No matter how angry she was.
你能相信这一切，真难得
It's sweet of you to believe that.
如此信任她
To believe in her.
但等到我们结束时
你就会知道你错得多离谱了
But by the time we're done here,
you'll know just how wrong you are.
听着，我找到了…
Hey, look, I found--
德弗罗女巫的事你说得没错
You were right
about the Deveraux witch.
找到那个神秘女巫克莱拉的线索了吗？
Find anything about Clara,
the mystery witch?
不多
Not much.
她曾是鸢尾花疗养院的护士
She was a nurse
at the Fleur-de-Lis Sanatorium.
认得她吗？
最上排，右边数来第二个
Recognize her?
Top row, second from the right.
不，不认识
No. I don't.
马赛尔
马赛尔？
Marcel-- Marcel?
需要我提醒你尼克劳斯和蕾贝卡
Do I need to remind you
that Niklaus and Rebekah
正在某处痛苦煎熬吗？
如果你知道什么…
are somewhere suffering horribly?
If you know something...
快点说
...talk.
疗养院，你可以在那里找到他们
Sanatorium.
That's where you'll find them.
你确定吗？你怎么知道？
You sure?
How do you know?
- 我就是知道
- 你怎么知道的？
-I just know.
-How do you know?
如果我没想错
If I'm right...
你就得知道我们到底面对的是什么
...you need to know exactly
what we're walking into.
我和蕾贝卡做了一件事
We did something, Rebekah and l.
我觉得女巫们在利用这事对付她
I think the witches
are trying to use it against her.
是你不会喜欢的事
It's something
that you're not gonna like.
你准备好看更多证据了吗？
Are you ready to see more proof?
- 你看到什么了？
- 我父亲的刀
-GENEVlEVE: What do you see?
-KLAUS: My father's blade.
我小时候它就不见了
It went missing
when I was a boy.
他把我揍得半死
确信是我偷走了它
He beat me half-to-death.
So sure I had stolen it.
我被打之后几周，蕾贝卡对我特别好
Rebekah was so kind to me
in the weeks after the beating
我就该意识到是她干的
I should have known
she was the culprit.
她最不能忍受别人说
女孩子不可以用武器
She never could stand weapons
were things not meant for girls.
不！
No!
我的妹妹
My sister.
蕾贝卡
Rebekah.
蕾贝卡！
Rebekah!
大半个世纪，我一直想知道
父亲是如何找到我们的
For the better part of a century,
I have wondered how Father found us.
我们到底是犯了什么愚蠢的错误
What foolish mistake
that we had made,
才毁了那处有着美好回忆
to destroy our time
in the one place
我们终于能称之为家的地方
that we could finally call home.
你知道吗
责怪自己
我甚至一度
，马赛勒斯
Do you know, I even blamed myself
for a time, Marcellus.
- 以利亚
- 尼克劳斯把你当儿子一样对待
-Elijah.
-Niklaus treated you like a son.
- 蕾贝卡…
- 我爱她，至今仍爱着她
-And Rebekah--
-I loved her. I still love her.
我们只是想在一起
All we ever wanted
was to be together
但只要克劳斯在
那就绝对不可能
but as long as Klaus was around,
that was never gonna happen.
但是，这些我想你根本不知道吧？
But hey, I guess you wouldn't know
anything about that, huh?
尼克劳斯得知真相后
你能想像他会有多暴怒
When Niklaus learns the truth,
there will be no end to his rage.
我不会让我妹妹承受他的怒火
I will not let my sister
suffer that wrath.
那我们得在他得知真相前找到他们
Then we need to get to them
before he learns the truth.
放弃吧，蕾贝卡
如今这已是不可避免的了
Just give it up, Rebekah.
It's inevitable at this point.
- 莎宾
- 其实我更喜欢莎莉丝特这名字
-Sabine.
-I prefer, Celeste, actually.
这些年来我有过很多名字
All these names I've had
over the years
我还是喜欢第一个
and I still prefer the first.
也许是因为我喜欢以利亚念它的感觉吧
Perhaps it was the way it sounded
on Elijah's lips.
就像是爱的宣言
Like a declaration of love.
他真是个撒谎高手
你们都是
Oh, he was a good liar.
All of you are.
随你怎么说我
但以利亚是个好人
Say what you will about me
but Elijah is a good man.
即使到最后还在为他辫护
Still defending him.
Even until the bitter end.
很好，我就指望着你们的家族亲情呢
Good.
I'm counting on that familial love.
那会毁了你们所有人
It'll be the ruin of you all.
现在克劳斯知道你做的事了
Now that Klaus knows
what you've done,
不复仇成功他是不会停止的
he'll never stop
until he's had his revenge.
他会杀了马赛尔，对你做出可怕的事
He'll kill Marcel
and do something horrible to you.
以利亚绝对不会原谅他
Elijah will never forgive him.
你的背叛最终会让兄弟反目成仇
Your betrayal will ultimately
pit brother against brother.
传说中的米卡森家族将分崩离析
And the fabled "Mikaelson bond"
will crumble.
- 我要杀了你，贱人
- 你已经杀过我了
-I'll kill you, you bitch.
-You already did.
不过在那时，我不是这副容貌
Though, at the time,
I wore a different face.
洁妮薇，我们得谈谈
私下谈
Genevieve, we need to talk.
Privately.
我可以的，你去吧
反正你也该清洗一下了
I'll be fine here, you go ahead.
You should wash up, anyway.
嘿
尽快把那个烧了
Hey.
Incinerate that as soon as you can.
你是另外那个护士，克莱拉
You were the other one.
Clara.
你不该来插手我的事
You should have minded
your own business.
我怀疑我的朋友被利用了
I suspected my friend
was being exploited.
这就是我的事
It was my business.
取消咒语，你疯了吗？
"Call it off."
Are you mad?
是我错了
I was wrong.
这太愚蠢，太冲动了
这会毁了我们的，洁妮薇
It was stupid, and impulsive
and it will ruin us, Genevieve.
不只是克劳斯，还有以利亚
Not just Klaus but Elijah too.
我自私地为了自己的幸福
冒着将家族摧毁的危险
I risked tearing our family apart
for my own, selfish happiness.
我请求你，求求你
不要让麦可来到这里
I am begging you. Please.
Don't bring Mikael here.
要是克劳斯发现我们所做的一切
If Klaus finds out
what we have done,
你所做的一切
what you have done...
克劳斯会杀了我
他会杀了我全家
Klaus will kill me.
He'll kill my entire family.
这正是我要你撤销咒语的原因
Which is exactly
why I need you to undo it.
这是不可能的
It doesn't work that way.
没办法撤销
麦可就要来了
There is no "undoing it."
Mikael is coming.
现在唯一的希望
就是告诉克劳斯真相
The only hope now
is tell Klaus the truth.
坦白我们所做的事情
Confess what we've done.
绝对不可以
That is not an option.
他会用匕首封住我
把我关在棺材里数个世纪
He will dagger me
and leave me in a box for centuries.
你什么都不许说
You will not say a word.
你利用了我
You used me.
自始至终，我们的友谊
你想要的只是我的能力
This whole time, our friendship,
all you wanted was a favor.
而现在你后悔了想要收回这一切？
And now, you want to take it back?
你不能
Well, you can't.
克劳斯不会怪我的
And I will not suffer
因为我只是太愚蠢选择相信了你
because I was foolish enough
to trust you.
那是个错误，我现在意识到了
It was a mistake.
I know that, now.
但这个错误会毁了我们的
But that one mistake
will destroy us.
这是你自找的
You brought this on yourself.
我不能和你一起被摧毁
I will not be destroyed
along with you.
我很抱歉，洁妮薇
I'm so sorry, Genevieve.
但如果你告诉尼克劳斯你召唤了麦可
But if you tell Niklaus
you summoned Mikael,
迟早你也是死路一条
you're dead, either way.
洁妮薇，没事吧？
Genevieve?
Is everything all right?
所以你把我也感染了
So you infected me too.
并魅惑护理员将我们隔离直到死去
Compelled the orderlies to keep us
in quarantine until we died.
（隔离病房）
幸运的是，我占用了另一个身体
CELESTE: Fortunately,
I just took another body.
洁妮薇就没那么幸运了
Genevieve wasn't so lucky.
既然她回来了
Well, now that she's back...
你就是那个不幸的人了
...you're the one
whose luck's run out.
抱歉
GENEVlEVE: I'm sorry.
我知道这很伤人
I know how much this hurts.
看到她的所作所为
To see what she did.
看清她的真正面目
To see who she really is.
但你必须要知道
But you needed to know.
你必须要看到
You needed to see it.
现在你都知道了，你可以复仇了
And now that you have,
you can take your revenge.
我们的复仇
Our revenge.
来吧，喝吧
Please.
Go ahead.
为了接下来的事你会需要力量
You'll need your strength
for what comes next.
蕾贝卡！
Rebekah!
我们应该分头找
We should divide the building.
我从这边开始，你去那边
I'll start at one end,
you at the other.
尼克，尼克，那不是真的
Nik. Nik, it isn't true.
我想要相信你，妹妹
I want to believe you, sister.
但你的表情出卖了你
But your face tells
a different story.
你躲不了我的，蕾贝卡
You cannot hide from me, Rebekah!
你也逃不掉
Nor can you run.
一切到此结束
This ends now.
你好啊，贱女巫
Hey, there, witch-bitch.
我们得好好聊一下了
You and l
are gonna have a little chat.
蕾贝卡！
KLAUS: Rebekah!
逃够了吗？
Tired of running?
我知道你有多享受追逐猎物的感觉
我不想给你更多这种快感
I know how much you enjoy the chase.
I'd sooner deny you the pleasure.
那我就用其他方式来享受吧
Well, then, I'll take my pleasures
in other ways.
我不会再让你插匕首躺棺材了
No more daggered-in-a-box
for you.
相信我，妹妹，你会怀念匕首的感觉的
Trust me, sister. You'll long
for what the dagger offered.
这个，就没那么仁慈了
This will be far less merciful.
要如何确切描述这把刀的用途呢？
How to describe exactly
what this blade does?
你用不着这么做，尼克
You don't have to do this, Nik.
当它插入你的心脏后
你将无法动弹
After I plunge this into your heart,
you will be immobilized,
处在一种撕心裂肺的无比痛苦之中
imprisoned in a state of raw,
inescapable anguish.
时间将毫无意义
Time loses all meaning.
如同人间炼狱
因为你的背叛
It's not unlike a living hell,
which I find rather fitting
我觉得这样处罚再适合不过了
given your treachery.
那就动手吧
如果这就是你想要的
Then, do it.
If that's what you really want.
我们跳过了你祈求饶恕的那段吗？
Are we skipping the part
where you beg for mercy?
祈求我原谅？
For forgiveness?
因为我本来真的很期待呢
Because I was really
looking forward to that.
不必了
I'll pass.
我很清楚这对我不会有什么好处
I know better than to think
it would do me any good.
那就这样了吗？
你放弃抵抗了
That's it, then?
You concede.
如同一头待宰的羔羊
Like a lamb to the slaughter.
你觉得父亲会怎么想你？
What would your father
think of you, now?
正是我想见的人
Just the man I wanted to see.
看着你死，蕾贝卡的惩罚
Rebekah's punishment
won't be complete
才算完整呢
until she watches you die.
尼克，召唤麦可是我的主意
Nik, it was my idea
to summon Mikael.
如果你要伤害谁，那一定就是我
If you're gonna hurt anyone,
it should be me.
对你的爱人真是忠贞啊
Such loyalty to your beloved.
你知道…
You know...
如果你给过我哪怕是一丁点的忠诚
If you had offered me
even a fraction of the same,
我也就不必这么做了
I wouldn't have to do this.
走吧
Go.
你们俩尽快逃走吧，越远越好
Both of you,
run as far and as fast as you can.
跑啊！
Run!
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）